Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2012, UWM Archival Collection 48; 28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - 2. Subject Files, 1959-2012
    - Women's Transit Service, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
As of May 24, 2013, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Adobe Reader XI was used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Acrobat PDF 1.4 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Contents List
- Records, 1915-2010, UWM Archival Collection 48; 19 cubic ft. (23 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - AA at UWM, 1977-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - A-Cad User Group, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Acapella Choir of UWM, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acceleration Club, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Access Party, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Accuracy in the Academics of Reporting, 1985-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Achieving Student Action Through Progress, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ACME Poetry, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - ACOA/AI-ANON/ACODF Women's Group, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Actors' Guild at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Admission Events, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adventures Outdoors (UWM), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adversary, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Club at UWM, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advisors of UWM Student Organizations, 1962-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Advocates for Life at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Advocates for Truth, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - African Liberation Support Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - African Students Association, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Afrika Incorporate, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Task Force at UWM, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Aikido Yoshinkai Club, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - ALANON/ACOA Welcome Home Group, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Aldo Leopold Conservation Club
    - 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Activities, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alioto for Alderman Student Chapter, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alioto for President Campaign Committee, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alive at UWM, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - All Night Klub (TANK), 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - All Night Party, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alliance for Animals, 1983-1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Alliance of Computer Enthusiasts at UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allied Health Program Student Organization, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Allied Health Student Association, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Angel Auxiliary Club, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Alpha Chi, 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alpha Chi Rho, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alpha Delta, 1951-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Delta Mu
    - 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1978-1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Alpha Delta Sigma, 1943-1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1959-1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi
    - 1956-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1957-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alpha Gamma Lambda, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Kappa Lambda, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi, 1957-1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi
    - 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1958-1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Alpha Phi, 1957-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Alpha Phi Omega
    - 1959-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - 1968-1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Alpha Sigma Alpha, 1950-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
  - Alpha Sigma Tau, 1975-1986 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Alpha Tau Delta, 1976-1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Alpha Tau Omega, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alpha XI, 1982-1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Alternative, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Alternative Axis Productions, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Alternative Broadcasting Systems, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alternative Concerts Group, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Alternative Energy for a Poetic Future, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Alternative Journalism Society, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Alternative Publications, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Alternative Recreation Club, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alternative Writers Workshop at UWM, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Counseling Association, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - American Friends of Revolutionary Iran at UWM, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Indian Graduate Council, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - American Indian Student Movement, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1972-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - American Institute of Architects Student Chapter, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - American Institute of Architecture Students, 1968-1994 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - American Marketing Association, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Medical Student Association, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - American Nazi Party, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Nuclear Society, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - American Society for Information Science, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - American Society for Personnel Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Society for Training and Development, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - American Society of Interior Designers, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - AMICI, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Amiga Bittmappers, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Amigos De Las Americas, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Amnesty International, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Analytical Psychology Fellowship at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Anna V. Day Dorm, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1972-1988 (Box 20, Folder 2-7)
    - 1989-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1-7)
  - Annual Security Report
    - 2007-2012
    - 2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Anthropology Club, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Anthros, 1960-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - APICS, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Apostolic Student Fellowship, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - April 24th Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Aqualens Cinema, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Arab Students Association, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Armenian Cultural Association, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Ars Musica, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Art Circle, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Art Club, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Art History Forum, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Art, Music and the Theatre, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Art of Listening Ensemble, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Art Student Cooperative, 1973-1985 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Art Students' League
    - 1957-1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 1992 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Art Students' Travel Association, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Artactics, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Artists for Peace in Vietnam, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Arts in Action, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Assassination Information Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Associated Students of UWM, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Associated University Broadcasters, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Associated Women Students, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Association for Childhood Education, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Association International of Students in Science of Economics and Commerce, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Association of Advanced Students in Education, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ATID, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Association of Black Artists, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Association of Computing Machinery, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Association of Students for Architecture, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Association of Women in Social Welfare, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Athletes in Action, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization Alumni Association, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Baccalaureate Student Nurses Organization of UWM, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - BACCHUS (Boost Alcohol Consciousness Concerning the Health of University Students), 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Backpacking Club, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Badminton Club, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Baha'i Club, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Ballroom Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bands at UWM, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Bangladesh Student Association at UWM, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Barely United Graduate Zoologists, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Baseball Club, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Be Proud UWM, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Beach Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Beer Party, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Believe, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Beta Chi
    - 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 1962-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Beta Phi Theta, 1924-1957 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Beta Pi, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Beta Sigma Psi Gamma, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Beta Tau Omego, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Biological Action Group, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Biological Science Organization, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Biology Club, 1940, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Biomedical Society, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bite Humor Society, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Black Achievement Organization, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Black and Gold, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Black Critic, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Black Cultural International Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Black Graduate Council, 1981-1988 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Black Mass Media Society, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Black Political Caucus, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Black Student Organization of the School of Social Welfare, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Black Students Psychological Association, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Black Students' Union, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Blue Key, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Bolton Hall Graduate Student Association, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bringing Excellence and Educational Reform, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Brotherhood Association of Independents, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Brotherhood of Ambitious Independents, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Brown for President Student Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Buddhist Studies and Meditation Group, 1982-1989 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Business and Professional Women at UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Business Oriented Student Society, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Camera Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Campus Action Party, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Campus Action Program, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Campus Activities Board, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Campus Advance, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Campus Affiliates of Project Youth, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Campus Arts Council, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Campus Bible Fellowship, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Campus Bible Study
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - 1994 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Campus Campaign for ERA, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Campus Carnival, 1951-1971 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Campus Chess Club, 1958-1985 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Campus Coalition for President Ford, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Campus Committee for Peace in Asia, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Campus Conservatives Club, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Campus Ecology for Education, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Campus Entertainment Organizers, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Campus Events Board (CEB), 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Campus Gamers Organization, 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Campus Gold, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Campus Graphics, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Campus Heterosexual Union, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Campus Party, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Campus Satelite, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Canterbury Association of Episcopal Students, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Cardinal Club, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cardinal Compass, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Cardinal Party, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Care for Cambodia, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - CASE Student Organization, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Caving Club, 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Ceramic Club, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Cercle Francais (French Club), 1957-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chamber Orchestra, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Change Progress and Reform, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Cheap Trips, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cheerleading Squad of UWM, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cheshire, 1957-1964, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Chess Club of UWM, 1958-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chess Masters, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Chi Alpha, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chi Beta Epsilon, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Chi Sigma Lambda, 1954-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Bible Study Group, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Book Club, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Christian Fellowship at UWM, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Chinese Student Library, 1978-1990 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Chinmoy Meditation Centre, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science Organization
    - 1957-1994 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Christian Students, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Christians on Campus, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chung Chin, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Church of Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Non-Mormon), 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Circle K Club, 1962-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Circle of Swords, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Cispes, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Citizens for Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Citizens Freedom Foundation-Information Service at UWM, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Citizens Utility Board, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Clams Fan Club, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Classical Civilization Club, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Club Espanol, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Club Jim Moody for Congress at UWM, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Coalition for Geopolitical Sanity, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Coalition of Concerned Students, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Coalition of Student Programmers, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Coalition United for Victory, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Coast to Coast Student Travel, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Colleagues in Action, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - College Choir, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - College Citizens of UWM, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - College Labor & Farm Party, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - College Panhellenic
    - 1965-1995 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Activities, 1958-1994 (Box 17, Folder 101-102)
  - College Volunteers, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles
    - 1980-1993 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - 1981-1983, undated (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Comedy Related Artistic Productions, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Commitment to Progress and Reform Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Committee for Informed Involvement, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Committee for Students' Concerns, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Committee in Solidarity with People of Iran, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Committee on Draft Education (CODE), 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Committee on Religious Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Committee to Elect Daryl Holter at UWM, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Committee to Fight the Cutbacks, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Common Cause, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Common Sense Party at UWM, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Communications and Mass Communications Association, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Community and Cultures Incorporated: Physics, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Concerned Students for International Rapprochement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Concerned Women for America, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Concert Choir, 1962-1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Concerts at UWM, 1982-1991 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Conference on Inter-American Student Projects, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Congress of Student Social Workers, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Congressional Information Network at UWM, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Conservation Club, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Consumer Affairs Student Organization, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cornerstone League, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Council for Exceptional Children, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Council for World Freedom, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Council of Engineering Student Organizations, 1975-1992 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Council on International Relations & United Nations Affairs, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Course and Faculty Evaluation Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Criminal Justice Student Association, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Crossroads
    - 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Lawsuit, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cuban Forum, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cultural Arts, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cultural Arts Student Express, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Cultural Organization of Persion Students, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Culture Abroad, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cycling Club, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Dalton Society, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Dames Club, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dance Association, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Dance Club, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Davison Cricket Appreciation Society, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Day Care Advocates, 1973-1986 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Dead Circus Company, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Deaf Student Association, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Dean of Instruction, 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dean of Men, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 48-52)
  - Debators at UWM, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Debate Team, 1957-1979 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Debate Team, Newsclippings and Flyers, 1962-1979 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Deeper Roots Fellowship, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Deliverance, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Delta Chi
    - 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Delta Chi Sigma
    - 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - 1957-1973 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Delta Fraternity, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Delta Kappa
    - 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - 1957-1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Delta Omicron, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Delta Phi Epsilon, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Delta Psi Chi Fraternity, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Delta Sigma Kappa
    - 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - 1957-1970 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Delta Sigma Rho, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1959-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Delta Tau Kappa, 1964-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Delta Zeta, 1950-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Delta Zeta Epsilon Sorority at UWM, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Demonstrations, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Deutscher Verein, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Disciples, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Disco Club, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ditrinetic Religious Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Divine Light Club, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dorado Club, 1957-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dragon Club, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Du Bois Club, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Duane Gay for Assembly Student Committee, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Earth and Magical Religions on Campus, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - East Side Bible Study, 1979-1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Echo, 1944-1950 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Eckankar Internaional Student Society, 1974-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Economic Club, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Economics Club, 1959-1967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Educational Psychology Graduate Association, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Educational Workers Industrial Union No. 620, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eight Fifty Nine Club, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Elementary Division, 1946-1956 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - The Empire, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - EMIT, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Emperor Mathematics Improvement Students, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - EMS, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Engineers' Club, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - English Club, 1957-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Environs Film Society, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Epilepsy Association of Southeast Wisconsin at UWM, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Episcopal Campus Rectory, 1962-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Equestrian Club, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Escape, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Escape From Milwaukee Club, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Eta Kau Pi, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Eta Sigma Phi, 1957-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ethiopian Famine and Refugee Relief Committee at UWM, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ethiopian Students Union, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Every Now and Then Film Society, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Exceptional Division, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Experimental Drama, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Experimental Music Society, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Facet Magazine, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Far-Out-Flix, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Federation of University Assistants, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fellowship of Benjamin Franklin, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Feminist Center of UWM, 1973-1984 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
  - Feminists for Life of Wisconsin, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Film Department Student Union, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Film Society at UWM, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fine Arts and Cultural Enrichment, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fine Arts Dance Club, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Fine Arts Music Club, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fireside Theatre Group, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Fly By Night Film Society, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Folk Dance Group, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Folk Sing, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Folklore Society, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - The Force, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Forte: Film, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Fortnightly, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Forty-Second Street Film Society, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Forum: American Israeli Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Forum/Major Speakers Organization, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Forum on Conscientious Objection and the Draft, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Fourth of July Club, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fraternities
    - 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Expansion, 1959-1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Policies, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Fraternity Scholarship Reports, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Free Speech, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Free Spirit Gang, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Free University, 1966-1977 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - French Club, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Friends Across the World, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Friends for a Cooperative Law School at UWM, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Friends for Brown, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Friends of Africa, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Friends of Eurythmy, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Friends of Free Schools, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Friends of Fun, Student Travel Club, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Friends of Kaleidoscope, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)